(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-29T13:13:25.105078",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Wait,
This is good!
I did it!
I infiltrated this place.
Success.
大成功じゃ！
A huge success!
に見つかり見られた！
I was spotted!
I can't believe you guys were watching me this whole time.
No...?!
To be honest, um, I did feel eyes on me, but um...
I knew you guys were watching, it's okay.
I knew you guys were watching, so it's okay.
Anyways, it's not the time to be talking about that because
today is a special day for me!
For me!
Today is...
Do you know what today is?
Say it, say it! Say it, say it!
Yeah, today is my birthday!
Happy birthday, Zeta!
Selamat ulang tahun!
I don't know. Well...
Oh, what? You're saying something?
Nope.
Skill issue? Skill issue?!
You're saying I'm a noob as a secret agent?
Bull... Okay, I can't say the rest, bull.
Your lies! You're lying! That can't be true!
I've been working hard. I've got the stamina,
and obviously the intelligence—IQ, IQ 200—and strength, you know?
Look at the power as well. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, anyways, don't you worry because I've got the perfect thing for today.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Have you ever heard of a... um... of a- of a secret agent school?
Yeah, so, uh, back in my days, back in my days,
I've been through hell and back, so I invited some students here so we can prove that I'm the best secret agent, okay?
So, um, we're gonna do some tests together to see how tough it is to become a professional secret agent like me, like me, like me, like me.
I'm a good example.
Anyways, it reminds me of my, um, old school days, you know?
But to be honest... to be honest, I don't know what we'll be doing yet, but...
Wait, oh crap, okay. It's almost time for the first test.
そうそう、あのテスト！
Right, right, that test!
そろそろ、早く行かないと！
We gotta hurry up and go!
わーい！
Yay!
なんかさ、あれ？
Hey, you see that?
ゾンビ？あれ？
A zombie? Huh?
あれなんかあれ、よくない？
Hey, doesn't that look like...
なんかみこちの威嚇ポーズにビビってる。
It looks terrified of Miko's intimidation pose!
あ！ビビってら！
Ah, it's scared!
あ、ビビってる！ビビってらー！
Ah, it's scared! It's totally scared!
あれ、これみこちゃんわかりました。
Huh, Miko-chan figured it out.
何？こいつ雑魚ゾンビです。
What? This guy's a trash mob zombie.
ざーこ！ざーこ！
Trash! Trash!
こいつ、どうせうぇむかも知れん。どうせ、うぇむゾンビ、みこちゃんむけ！みこちゃんむけ！いけ！
This guy's probably weak anyway. A weak zombie, made for Miko-chan! Go!
ポンコツ〜！
Useless~!
え？聞けてる？もしかして、あ、じゃみこちゃんも言って？
Huh? Can it hear? Wait, then Miko-chan, you say it too?
ざーこ！ざーこ！
Trash! Trash!
聞いてる聞いてる！珍しく、珍しく聞いてる！
It's listening! It's actually listening for once!
ちょっと弱々ゾンビたんじゃない？全然怖くないですけどね。
Isn't this a super weak little zombie? It's not scary at all.
弱々かんまー。
Weakling vibes.
弱々かんまー！
Weakling vibes~!
あ、出た！
Ah, it's out!
おお、出た！
Oh, it's out!
おい！ゾンビ！何してんの！怖がらせろって言ったでしょ！
Hey! Zombie! What are you doing?! I told you to scare them!
ゾンビおめでとう！
Congrats on being a zombie!
何このゾンビ？
What is this zombie?
あれは弱々ゾンビ。
That's a weakling zombie.
星軍トスクールの最初のテストにお招きしたけど、
We invited you to the first Star Troop School test, but...
ゾンビも新入生なのかな？
Are zombies also incoming students?
新入生なの？新入生なの？
Are they a new student? Are they?
大丈夫なのかな？
Will they be okay?
そうなんだ。
Is that so.
そうだ、でも言葉通じないけどさ、ゾンビに。ゼータは言葉いろんなこと話せるよね。
That's right, but zombies don't understand words, right? Zeta can speak all sorts of words, though.
ゾンビとも喋れるんじゃないの？
Wouldn't she be able to talk to zombies too?
やめてやめて。やめて。オッケーオッケーオッケー。
Stop, stop, stop. Okay, okay, okay.
うぇ、いけ！
Ugh, go!
ちょっと弱そうか？
Might be a bit weak?
え、でも、噛み殺してる？
Eh, but is it biting to death?
よし、できた！
Alright, done!
できた！
Done!
おい！ゾンビ！
Hey! Zombie!
何してんの！
What are you doing?!
怖がらせろって言ったでしょ！
I told you to scare them!
オリーさん、何やってたのよ！？
Ollie-san, what were you doing?!
怒ってる！怒ってる！
She's mad! She's mad!
Apologies.
どうやら弱っちいゾンビを送っちゃったみたい。申し訳ないわね。
I guess I sent over weak zombies. Sorry about that.
ともかく、今日はみなさんにサプライズテストをご用意しました。
Anyways, I prepared a surprise test for you all today.
シークレットエージェントにふさわしいか、確かめてみましょう。
Let's see if you're fit to be a secret agent.
なんだかわかんないけど受ける！
I don't really get it, but I'll take it!
なんだかわかんないけど受けてみろか！受けてみよう！
I don't really get it, but let's try taking it! Let's take it!
では、この箱の中身を当てて貰うテストになりますー！
This test will require you to guess what's inside this box!
探索能力試験。箱の中に何が入っているのかを当ててもらう、1人30秒間ずつ触れることができる
Investigative skills test. Guess what's inside the box within 30 seconds each.
箱の中身！？こんなん！
What's inside the box?! Like this!
ラウンド1では、箱の中に何が入っているのかを当ててもらう、1人30秒間ずつ触れることができる。楽しんでくださいね。
For Round 1, you can feel the object inside for 30 seconds only. Have fun.
キャント・ウェイ・トゥ・シー・ユア・リアクションズ。
Can't wait to see your reactions.
いいリアクション期待してるよだって。
She says she's expecting good reactions.
完全に理解してるから。
Because we completely understand.
本当かよ！怒ってるってこと？怒ってるってこと？
Really?! Does that mean she's mad? Does it?
じゃあ、AZKi先輩からかな？
Then, should AZKi-senpai go first?
任せてくださいよ。頑張って！
Leave it to me. Do your best!
えーるちゃんは、これあさみんなで協力してだよね？協力して、まあまあまずは、箱の中身、魅力を伝えることに集中したいと思います。いいよー！はい！
Botan-chan, we're all cooperating for this, right? Cooperating, well first of all, I want to focus on conveying the charm of what's inside the box. Alright! Yes!
3, 2, 1, スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
え？え？なんだこれ？え？コードのような？コード？コードのえ？違う。コードのものではないぞ。
Eh? Eh? What is this? Eh? Like a cord? A cord? A cord's... no. It's not a cord.
え？動いてる？動いてる？いっちょいっちょ！
Eh? It's moving? It's moving? It's a little, a little!
え、なんか、じたばたしてます。じたばた。じたばた、なんか、動いてる動いてる！動いてるんだって！え、これ？
Eh, like, it's thrashing around. Thrashing. Thrashing, it's moving! It's moving, seriously! Eh, what is this?
え？何々何々？え、なんか動いている、けど！
Eh? What what? Eh, it's moving, but!
タイムアップ！なんだなんだ？
Time's up! What was that?
え？なんかフォームがわからない。
Eh? I can't figure out its form.
変の機械なんじゃない？なんか足がばたばたしてるみたいな。
Isn't it some weird machine? Like legs kicking around.
えーー！？えーー！？やばい！大丈夫それ！？
Eeeh?! Eeeh?! Oh no! Is that okay?!
じゃあ、みおがーん！スタート！
Then, Mio-gong! Start!
おお！おお！おお！
Oh! Oh! Oh!
怖い怖い怖い！何々何々？
Scary, scary, scary! What is it?
でも分かったかも、これうち。え？あーー！なるほど！はいはいはい！はいはいはいはい！
But I might know what this is. Eh? Ahh! I see! Yes yes yes! Yes yes yes yes!
ああ、元気ですね！
Ah, it's energetic!
元気だね！元気ですけど！
It's energetic! It is energetic, but!
完全に生きてます！生きてるやん！
It's completely alive! It's totally alive!
あ、元気だったな。
Ah, it was energetic.
すっごい元気だった。
It was super energetic.
え、なんか穏やかな表情。元気だったよねー。
Eh, such a calm expression. It was energetic, wasn't it?
ゴッドハンドで、よろしかっただけますでしょうか。
Shall we have you experience the Gott Hand?
3、2、1、ゴー！
3, 2, 1, Go!
待って、絶対嫌だ。
Wait, I definitely don't want this.
うわぁ！わー！
Whoa! Ah!
やだ、やだ！えっ？
No, no! Eh?
なんか冷たい！いやだ！
It feels cold! No way!
なんかね、に触れた模様。
It feels like... something touched me.
なになに！？
What is this!?
やめて！やめて！
Stop it! Stop it!
ガチですか？
Is this for real?
ガチのやつ！
It's the real deal!
待って、冷たっ！
Wait, it's so cold!
ねえ、やばいって！
Hey, this is bad!
深刻な表情。おっ、おっ、おっ。
A serious expression. Oh, oh, oh.
分かった？
Did you figure it out?
全然わかんない。
I have no idea at all.
終わりだよ！ え、終わりだよ！
Time's up! Eh, time's up!
えっ、ゴッドハンド？ゴッドハンド？どう？
Eh, Gott Hand? Gott Hand? How was it?
ぶるーってなって、ビュンビュン動く。
It goes brrr and moves flying around.
めちゃきもい！
So gross!
じゃあ次は！
Okay, next!
じゃあ次は誰だ！じゃあ次は誰だ！
Then who's next! Then who's next!
ゼータちゃんから！
From Zeta-chan!
ベスティア・ゼータの挑戦
Vestia Zeta's Challenge
いきますよ！いきます！
Here we go! Let's go!
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
怖っ！えっ、触れ！
Scary! Eh, touch it!
えっ、これ生きてるやん！
Eh, this is alive!
えっ、やだ、待って待って、動かないわ、動かない！
Eh, no, wait wait, it doesn't move!
えっ、えっ、これ何？
Eh, eh, what is this?
ちゃんと触っています。
She's touching it properly.
何これ、形を確認しているのでしょうか。
What is this? Are they confirming the shape?
大丈夫かな。え、飛んでる？
Is it okay? Eh, is it flying?
これ飛んでる？飛んでる？なんか飛びそうではあるよね。
Is it flying? It seems like it might fly.
いや飛びそうだよね、これ。
Yeah, it feels like it'll fly, right?
あ、飛びそう！うわっ！生きてる！
Ah, it looks like it'll fly! Whoa! It's alive!
生きているの？何なの？
Is it alive? What is it?
いや、これちょっと、え、でもこれみんなでね、うわー！
Man, this is... Eh, but everyone together, whoa!
だから、だから、あそこから合わせてね、誰かの答えを...。
So, let's combine from there, someone's answer...
なんかプロペラ...？なんか、羽がついてたのかな？
Something like a propeller...? Did it have feathers?
マジで、私たちのがブルーってなってから、うわっ！
Seriously, after ours went brrr, whoa!
アヒルとかの足が、こう、なんか、パタパタパタパタみたいな、こう、パタパタパタパタみたいな、なんか、そういうおもちゃ。
Like a duck's feet or something flapping like patapata.
みお先輩は？
Mio-senpai?
これはズバリ、カエルのおもちゃです！ピョコピョコピョコ！
This is precisely... a frog toy! Pyokopyoko!
プロペラってしてたってこと？
You mean it was doing propeller stuff?
ゼータちゃん、みんなのこの、解答まとめを...。
Zeta-chan, please summarize everyone's answers...
えー！回答をまとめてください！
Eh! Please summarize the answers!
みお先輩の答えで。おっ！
Mio-senpai's answer. Oh!
私自信満々だったもん！いや、確かに自信満々だったんだ、これ間違えてたらうちのプロペラなんだわ。
I was so confident! If this is wrong, it's Uchi's propeller.
カエルのおもちゃかな？
Maybe a frog toy?
みんなのアレだからね、まあまあまあまあ。
Since it's everyone's choice, well, you know.
じゃあカエルのおもちゃね！
Then a frog toy!
おっ、よくできました！
Oh, well done!
やったー！カエルのおもちゃだ！えっ、すごーい！えっ、すごすぎる！
Yay! It's a frog toy! Eh, amazing! Too amazing!
えっ、すごいみおちゃん！えっ、何がポイントだったんですか？
Eh, amazing Mio-chan! What was the key point?
触った感じがピタピタしてて...。いや、それもピタピタもあれだ、金属素材だったから。
The feel of touching it was slimy... That was because it was metal.
ぴょんぴょんってしてたから。そうそうそう。
Because it was hopping around. Exactly.
だから、これ、カエルのおもちゃっぽいなって思ったんだよね。
So I thought, this seems like a frog toy.
すごい！素晴らしい！
Amazing! Wonderful!
じゃあ、次の問題、お願いします！
Now, the next question, please!
じゃあ、うちが行ってみますか。ゴッドハンドみおん、行きますか。
Shall Uchi go try it? Gott Hand Mion, shall I go?
ゴッドハンドみおん、ゴッドハンドみおんです。
Gott Hand Mion, Gott Hand Mion.
大神ミオの挑戦
Ookami Mio's Challenge
スタート！わっ！
Start! Whoa!
がんばれ！何、何、なんか...。こわい、こわい、ほら！
Hang in there! What, something... Scary, look!
手が怖がっている！
Her hands are getting scared!
えっ、何が？嘘でしょ、何これ！？
Eh, what? No way, what is this!?
これは何だ、なんだよこれ、気持ち悪い！
What is this, what is this, gross!
えっ？えっ？気持ち悪い！
Eh? Eh? Gross!
気持ち悪い、気持ち悪い！えっ、何これ、何これ！？
Gross, gross! Eh, what is this, what is this!?
えっ、怖い、怖い、怖い！えっ？
Eh, scary, scary, scary! Eh?
いや、分かった、分かったじゃないのその反応！
No, I figured it out, or rather, that reaction!
えっ、何！？
Eh, what!?
いや、いやー！いやー！
No, no way! No way!
大げさにやってるでしょ！
You're exaggerating, right?
なんかやだ！ちょっと行ってみて、行ってみて、これちょっと...
Something's scary! Go try it, this thing...
あずき行け。あずき、頑張れ！
AZKi go. AZKi, do your best!
AZKiの挑戦
AZKi's Challenge
スタート！
Start!
やだ！やっぱそうだよね！
No way! As expected!
どうなの？え、何？え、何？
How is it? Eh, what? Eh, what?
いや、その反応になるって、もしや、もしやしてます。
No, for that kind of reaction to happen, could it be.
えっ、待って、待って。
Eh, wait, wait.
ヒントは？
The hint is?
もしや、もしや、もしや...。
Could it be, could it be, could it be...
なんか、ベタベタしてた。
It was kind of sticky.
えっ、キモい！何それ？気持ち悪い！
Eh, gross! What is that? Creepy!
えっ、これ、多分...。これは何かのパーツって言われたらむずいんだけど。
Eh, this, probably... If you say it's some part, it's hard.
えー、なんかちょっと心にダメージ受けるよね、これ。
Man, it kind of damages your heart, doesn't it?
ゼータ、行くか！
Zeta, shall we go!
ベスティア・ゼータの挑戦
Vestia Zeta's Challenge
スタート！わー！
Start! Whoa!
初手、初手驚くよね？
You'd be surprised right at the start, wouldn't you?
最初は驚くよね、これ。
You'd definitely be surprised at first, right?
えー？
Eh?
えー？でも、
Eh? But...
柔らかい、柔らかい。
It's soft. It's soft.
柔らかい。
Soft.
優しい。
So gentle.
優しい？柔らかい。
Gentle? Soft.
これに関してはずっと、あのゼタの感覚が狂ってるかもしれない。
As for this, maybe Zeta's sense of touch has been completely broken all this time.
えー？
Eh?
何々何々？余裕って怖いよ。
What, what, what? Being too confident is scary.
え、いいのか？
Huh, is that really okay?
ここで。
Here?
いいのか？いいのかここで。
Is that okay? Is that okay here?
うーん。
Hmm.
じゃあ、みこ先輩がんばってね。
Well then, Miko-senpai, do your best!
出た！ごとな！出たごとな！
It came out! Gotona! It came out gotona!
いやこれチュートリアルクションだよ！チュートリアルクション狂った！
No, this is tutorial action! The tutorial action is broken!
来た！どこがチュートリアルクション？
It's here! How is this a tutorial action?
待って、待って、ためらっています。
Wait, wait, she's hesitating.
手をいれることをためらっているが、ためらうよね、これ一度聞いたもん。
She's hesitating to put her hand in, but of course she'd hesitate, she's heard this once before.
なんか、言っ…ミコを推すきじゃないか。
Wait, something... Isn't this pushing Miko?
待って、待って。何これ？とげとげするよな。
Wait, wait. What is this? It's all spiky.
食べ物？いや、そんなことはない。
Food? No, no way.
バカね。
How foolish.
ちょっとやばいことが起きてるんじゃないか。
Something a bit dangerous might be happening here.
やばいこと、箱の中で事件が起きている。
Something dangerous, an incident is happening inside the box.
マスクをしとったと思うんだよね。だからうちはピエロなんじゃないかと思いました。
I thought she was wearing a mask. So I thought maybe it's a clown.
えっと、白い、白塗りの女性の顔！
Um, a white, face-painted woman's face!
こええよ！
That's terrifying!
マスク？マスクか？マスク？
Mask? A mask? A mask?
その答え、こええよ。
That answer is terrifying.
おそらく…うん…YAGOOのカツラ。
Probably... yeah... YAGOO's wig.
絶対にカツラだったと思うんだよ。
I'm sure it was a wig.
ロングヘア、いやロングヘアYAGOO。
Long hair, no, long hair YAGOO.
そうだよね、可能性、可能性高い。
That's right, high possibility, high possibility.
名探偵みこ先輩に心証を…
Let's trust ace detective Miko-senpai's intuition...
答えはロングヘアYAGOO！
The answer is long hair YAGOO!
あっ、ちゃー。残念だね。
Oh dear. Too bad.
不正解です！
Wrong answer!
なんか怖いんだけど。
But that's so scary.
当たってた！
It was correct!
見えてた！
She could see it!
見えてたの？見えてるよ！
She could see it? She could see it!
見えてんの？怖っ！
She could see it? Creepy!
見えてんの怖っ！
It's so scary she could see it!
次のお題、お願いします！
Next prompt, please!
じゃ、こっから行ってみますか。名探偵、名探偵。
Well then, shall we go from here? Ace detective, ace detective.
名探偵、名探偵頼むよ。
Ace detective, ace detective, I'm counting on you.
ここここ！
Here, here!
待って、待って。濡れてる。
Wait, wait. It's wet.
なんか今日の絶叫出たけど大丈夫？
I let out quite a scream today, but is this okay?
実況してよ！実況実況！
Do live commentary! Commentary, commentary!
なんかチクチクしてて、チクチク…
It feels prickly, prickly...
どういうこと？
What does that mean?
なんか、濡れてるって！
It's wet, they say!
濡れてる？濡れてる？濡れてる？
Wet? Wet? Wet?
全部ニあの、トゲトゲがあります！
There are prickles all over it!
全部ニトゲトゲがあるの？いっぱいある？
There are prickles all over? There are a lot of them?
いっぱいいるってな。
There are a lot of them, huh.
え、何々何々？いっぱいる。
Huh, what what what? There are a lot.
どうする？AZKi先輩ほうがいいかな？
What should we do? Would AZKi-senpai be better?
で、せーの判断できるのか？
So, can we make a judgment on the count of three?
AZKi先輩、ゴー！
AZKi-senpai, go!
え？何？
Eh? What?
ん？なんか濡れてる？濡れてる？
Hmm? Is it wet? Is it wet?
やっぱ濡れてるんだ。やっぱ
It really is wet. It really is...
なんか、湿っ、湿って、湿っています。
It's kind of moi-, moist, it's moist.
てか、結構高めなんだこれ。
I mean, this is pretty high up.
どういうこと？え, 何これ？
What do you mean? Eh, what is this?
ん、トゲトゲした、なんか球体のような、球体？
Um, a spiky, kind of sphere-like, sphere?
球体と、その下にもトゲトゲしたものが…
A sphere, and underneath that something spiky...
トゲトゲがいっぱいある感じ？
Like there are lots of spikes?
痛くはないけど…痛くはない？
It doesn't hurt, but... it doesn't hurt?
え、これなんだ？
Eh, what is this?
なんだろう？なんだろう？
I wonder what it is? I wonder what it is?
全然わかんない。え、めっちゃむずいんだ、じゃあ。
I have no idea at all. Eh, so it's super hard then.
なんだこれ！
What is this?!
なんか湿ってるー！
It's kind of moist!
みおちゃんすか？ねえ次。
Mio-chan, right? Hey, next.
いやー、最後ゼタに決めてもらおっかな。
Man, maybe I'll have Zeta decide at the end.
いやだなぁ、その感覚を聞いた状態でやる、触るのはちょっとやだかも。
No way, after hearing about that texture, touching it might be a bit unappealing.
いやだなぁ、濡れてるって前情報でやだ。
Gross, the prior info that it's wet makes it unappealing.
濡れてる…あ、やっぱ濡れてるな。
Wet? Ah, it really is wet.
濡れてる？濡れてる？本当だ、濡れてるー！
Wet? Wet? It's true, it's wet!
えー、けど…濡れてるけど…
Uh, but... it's wet, but...
なんか硬くて、硬い下にたくさんいる！たくさんいるぞ！
It's kind of hard, and underneath the hard part there are tons of them! There are tons!
一体なんだよ！何これ？
What on earth is it?! What is this?
これは…
This is...
なんだ？え、でも…
What is it? Eh, but...
あんまり見かけないやつの気がする。
I feel like it's something you don't see very often.
見かけない…見かけない。
You don't see it... you don't see it.
これ、おむずいんじゃねえ？
How does this work?
おむずいんだ！
It's so hard!
おむずいんだ！ぜた！いけ！いけ！
It's really hard!
いけ！いけ！がんばれ、ぜた！
Go, Zeta! Go!
おっけー、おっけー。それでは！
Okay, okay. Here we go!
ベスティア・ゼータの挑戦
Vestia Zeta's Challenge
Start!
うわ！
Woah!
おー！
Ooh!
うわ！
Woah!
あ！
Ah!
あ、おっけ、おっけ。
Ah, okay, okay.
お、おっけ！
Oh, okay!
お、おっけ、おっけ！
Oh, okay, okay!
はやく、はや！
Hurry up!
え、おっけ。待って、これさ。
Eh, okay? Wait, what is this?
おっけ、わかる。
Okay, I see.
我々はあんまり馴染みないけど。
Well, we aren't very familiar with it,
ぜたは馴染みあるの？
Zeta's definitely familiar with it.
馴染みあるの？あるの？
Does she have them?
もしかしたら。え、何？
If so, then...
これいっぱい触ったとことわるか。え？え？
She touched it a lot, so maybe she's picky?
馴染み深い。
Familiar?
馴染み深いんだよ、ゼータにとっては。
It's familiar to Zeta, right?
そう、そう、いや。
Yeah.
なんだろう？
What is it?
我々にしたらちょっと難しいかも。
If it's us, it might be hard.
タイムアップ！
Time's up!
いえーい！おっけ、おっけ！
Yay! Okay, okay!
これはね、うん、うん、うん、うん。
This is... Hmm, hmm, hmm.
おそらくこれは……
Could this be...
ウニの仲間。
Sea creatures?
ウニ？ウニ？
Sea? Sea?
アキの答えは……
Aki's answer is...
コケ！
Kelock!
なんかその、ちょっと、ちょっとずついっぱい中生えている感じ？
Wait, it's kind of...
でも確かに湿ってたよね。そう、湿ってたし。
But it was definitely damp, right?
うちの答えはライチ！
Our answer is lychee!
ライチ！
Lychee!
ゼータはね、たぶん……
Zeta probably...
なんか、インドネシアの果物と近いかも。
It's close to Indonesian fruits, maybe?
いっぱい、なんか、トゲトゲ、トゲトゲ。
Full of... Spiky, spiky.
なんていう食べ物なの？
What kind of food is that?
名前はランブータン！ランブータン！
The name is Rambutan!
ランブータン！
Rambutan!
でもわかんない、ここにはランブータンはないのかも。
But I don't know, is there rambutan here?
でも、自信も！
I have confidence!
そうだよ！ゼータが一番わかってたよ！
That's right, Zeta knew it best!
一番そう、自信あったじゃん！
Yeah, you were confident!
ね、じゃあそれでいきましょうよ。
Right? Let's go with that!
答えは、せーの、ランブータン！
The answer is, ready, go!
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding!
Ding, ding, ding, ding!
正解でーす！
Correct answer!
ランブータン！
Rambutan!
ちょっと待って、うちライチとか言ってたけど、全然違うじゃん。
Wait a minute, I said lychee...
そっそっそ。えっ！これ！
Look at that!
ライチの味かすっかも。
It looks like lychee.
にてる。うーん。
It's similar.
え？美味しいよこれ？初めて見た。
Is this delicious?
甘いの？甘いんだ！
Is it sweet?
ちょっと甘っぽい。
It's a bit sweet.
甘っぽい。美味しい果物にに出会いました。
A sweet fruit.
正解の答も不正解の答も
There seems to have been correct
ありましたね。
and incorrect answers.
でも……
But...
ゼータ！
Zeta!
どうやらあなたの推理力は
It seems like your investigative skills
まだまだみたいだね？
are not quite up to par yet.
もっと頑張らないと。
You need to work harder.
つまり、そう……
Or, in other words...
スキルの問題ね！
Skill issue!
見て、スキルの問題のゼータだ！
Oh, look at her with the skill issues!
ああっ、怒っちゃった！
She's getting mad!
あらあら！
Oh dear!
まったく、こんなのも解けないなんて！
Wow, you can't even solve that!
みんな、よくやったわ！
Everyone else, you did great!
次のテストも頑張ってくださいね！
Good luck on the next test!
またね！
See y'all!
ゼータも頑張ったのにさ。
Zeta worked hard too, you know.
さっき笑ったの？
Did you laugh just now?
ちょっと、なめてた？なめてたね？
Don't lick him! Don't lick him!
なめてんじゃねえよ！
You shouldn't lick him!
なめてんじゃねえよ、お前！
Don't lick him, you!
一生懸命やったんだよ。
She worked so hard.
あんまりいじめるな！いじめるなよ！
Don't bully him so much!
あずき、あずき！
Azuki, Azuki!
あずきちゃん優しい、優しい。
Azuki is so nice.
もっと床に這いつくばりなさい！
You should lie down on the floor more.
あずきさま！
Azuki-sama!
ありがとね、みんな来てくれて本当に。
Thank you, everyone!
おめでとう！おめでとう！
Congratulations!
なんか、あと、今日は集めてくれてありがとね、本当に。
And thank you so much for coming today!
次のテストの時間だから、行ってくるね！
It's time for the next test, so I'll be going!
やった！やった！勝ちました！
I won! I won!
ゾンビ、もっと祝いなさいよ！祝いなさいよ、もっと！
Zombie, you should celebrate more!
ゼータを祝いなで！
Celebrate Zeta!
Wait, there's like a ring.
Wait, is this like a boxing ring?
Wait, what am I gonna have to do here?
No way. Are we going to have to fight?
I'm not good at fighting, though.
Like, I mean, I can try.
I mean, I can try.
Happy birthday, Zeta!
Long time no see!
This is Amelia Watson,
hololive EN's number one time-traveling detective!
How've you been?
I've been good! How are you?
Ah, glad to see you're doing well!
Yeah, I prepared the second test,
but we also have other transfer students.
Let's call them in now!
Don't let the first contestant's size fool you!
People tremble...
People tremble when they hear her name and her infamous line!
Small but mighty, always rock hard. I'm rocking in!
Please welcome... Koseki Bijou!
Happy birthday, Zeta.
Today, I'm rock hard just for you.
Thank you. I'm honored.
Coming to the ring, she's the hero we didn't ask for, but somehow still believe in!
She's everyone's last hope, because all the good ones were busy!
Her line is: "Meet your end, and... despair! Haiyah!"
Please welcome... IRyS!
Just a one-love.
Happy birthday, Zeta.
I'm taking you down.
Ladies and gentlemen, hide your dumbbells and protect your ego, because this grim reaper doesn't just reap souls, she rips the gym apart!
Her favorite line is: "Only time can out-bench me."
Please welcome... Mori Calliope!
Happy birthday, Zeta!
Good! Everyone has gathered, right?
This is probably a big surprise, huh?
And I'm sure you're all wondering what kind of test this is gonna be! Anyone have any guesses?
Don't say ground pounding.
Oh, correct! We're holding a physical test using this long stick with these Bazo weights to determine if you are fit enough to pass off as a secret agent!
Bazo? Oh my god. Okay, that looks heavy.
Okay, okay. For level 1 of the physical test!
First, lift Bazo from the ring mat up to your hips as many times as you can within 30 seconds!
For level 2, the mat will be bumpy!
You'll do the same thing as many times as you can within 30 seconds!
And for the last level, you'll stand on the bumpy mat and balance a cup on your head! Make sure you don't drop it, and lift Bazo up!
Well then, are you guys ready? Let's go!
Okay, who's ready for the physical test?
Okay, and maybe we should have Bijou start first.
I got it!
You rock hard muscles! Lift that Bazo lift!
Okay, are you ready? Yeah!
Pop it, start!
Time's up!
Bijou! Level 1: 21!
So IRyS...
I got out of that.
Like you?
Yes, I'm a pro at pumping people up!
Yes, my pro potential!
Start!
Time's up!
Is it a tie?
It's a tie! It's a tie!
Oh, you said it's more of a speed thing, isn't it?
Show us ready? Start!
Time's up!
Anyway, that was me.
So, what's your score?
Level 1, 29.
Like I said...
Okay, Zeta, show us what you're made of.
Okay, I got this.
You're going to count up for me?
Of course.
You ready?
Yeah.
All right.
Start!
Time's up!
Zeta, Level 1, 30.
That was safe!
She is a secret agent after all.
Okay.
Now who's ready for Level 2?
I don't know about this one.
Wait, wait a minute.
That's not fair.
She has an advantage.
Okay, start!
Time's up!
Bijou, Level 2, 34.
Come on, don't show the world again.
You have to prove to the world that you are strong.
Take your time.
How does it feel?
Tell me when you're ready.
Ready?
Start!
Time's up!
IRyS, Level 2, 20.
I'm not going to go that hard.
Calli's going to help me.
I'll try to just do my best.
Tell me when you're ready.
Okay, start!
Time's up!
You got more than that on your first time.
Yeah, your form was perfect.
I think I got 33.
And the final count is 32!
I'll take it!
Step on those pebbles like they're what?
If it gives you permission. Yeah, we were given permission.
She's going Super Saiyan! Yeah!
Something's coming out of me.
All right, Zeta, you're ready? Yeah!
3, 2, 1, go!
1, 2
3, 4, 5
6, 7, 8
9, 10, 11
12, 13, 14
15, 16, 17
18, 19, 20
21, 22, 23
24, 25, 26
27, 28, 29
30, 31, 32
33, 34, 35
36, 37, 38
Time's up!
I'm glad you guys are having fun!
Level 3 of the physical test is gonna be pretty tough, though.
You guys ready?
For Level 3, I've got a little something...
behind me, which is a...
A cup! A cup!
Would you like a cup of tea?
Um, maybe later. Another time, oh?
Well, while you guys are stepping on the bumpy mat...
we're also going to be balancing this cup on top of our head like this!
Yeah, you'll have to use the mat.
It's a combination of everything!
And while lifting as well, of course.
Yeah, it doesn't affect us at all! It doesn't affect us at all!
Okay, okay. Crown me!
Give me the crown. Crown the princess!
Oh, there you go! It's so over! It's so over!
Are you ready, the people? Are you ready?
Oh yeah, remember to use your butt and your legs! Core and your legs!
Okay, four?
Yes.
Are you ready? Are you ready?
Start!
1, 2, 3
4, 5, 6
7, 8, 9
10, 11, 12
13, 14, 15
16, 17, 18
19, 20, 21
22, 23, 24
25, 26, 27
Time's up!
How many was that? I like how the cup was like stuck on her head.
Yeah, that was funny. And then it turned over and it was hot on her head! Oh, that was so funny!
28! You got 28!
Pyramid! It's a pyramid!
I have... Princess! I have a beautiful posture!
Yeah, exactly. Show us the posture!
And this is a whole other point because you have to keep it on your head.
Wait, wait a sec. Don't put it on me yet! Don't put it on me yet!
Okay, you may place it on my head, the lady.
Here goes. Thank you all. It's beautiful. Not to my coronation.
3, 2, 1, start!
1, 2, 3
4, 5, 6
7, 8
9, 10, 11
Time's up!
I don't know how you guys did this! Get out of here! You stupid cup!
Level 3 - 10.
Maybe my good form will come in handy here. Yeah, exactly. You may place the tiara on my head.
You have to step on it first.
Come on. You have to feel the pain before the game. The pain before the game is beauty.
I'll place it on top of the crown so you have double crown.
Okay. Are you ready, cult? Maybe. Okay, maybe.
3, 2, 1, start!
1, 2, 3
4, 5
6, 7
It did not fall!
It didn't fall!
That was my goal!
Yes, that's 24! And I didn't lose the cup even once!
You sure? Yeah, maybe there was tape.
Maybe there was tape. I didn't check that thing.
Is it? Is it not?
Super glue? Put it on her head! Put it on her head!
What's really test it. Let's really get in there. You're going to use me as the... the test dummy, right?
Let's really test it. Let's really get in there. You're going to use me as the... test dummy, right?
It's Zeta's turn.
My birthday! Yeah. And you know what?
Directly right in the center of your head so that it's less likely to fall off.
This is like the best birthday ever.
Aw. Yay, I'm glad. Now then, are you ready?
Watch, watch, watch! Only one life!
You did it! 26 is the final number!
26! Yay! Wow!
Is this... Does Zeta's score is what I think it is? I think so!
Is anyone keeping score? Staff-son has been keeping score for us.
Yes! You are the winner! You are the winner! I am the winner! Yeah, you're the winner.
What are the scores again? What matters is what's inside.
Seems like you guys completed the test! Woohoo!
Some of you were able to lift pretty well.
Maybe not for some, though.
It was so much fun just watching!
But come on, Zeta! You're the birthday girl!
You should be showing us your crazy skills or something!
Prove it to us next fest, okay?
Well then, thank you for having me! This is Amelia Watson signing off. Until next time!
Bye! Bye-bye!
She does have really high standards, okay?
Even if you won... Well, she is the detective, like, yeah.
Not enough. Everybody is getting better.
Tasukete! Laplus Darknesss!
Help me! Laplus Darknesss!
Natsuiro Matsuri!
Bokobokobo—Kobo Kanaeru at your service! Let me be your sun to shine your day! Eheh!
Zeta, happy birthday!
I already told them what to do before you came here, so they know the rules!
We're gonna be testing your aim skills with this water gun!
In shooting level 1, we will see how many immobile targets you can hit within 30 seconds!
In level 2, we will see how many moving targets you can hit within 30 seconds!
And level 3 will test if you can hit the targets on the moving zombie!
Who do you think is the best shooter here?
Tota-tachi minna nanto FPS yatterun dane!
You guys are all playing FPS games, huh!
Sou da ne. Watashi wa yattenai kedo ne.
That's true. Though I don't play them myself.
さあ、がんばろ。
Come on, let's do our best.
誰が勝つんでしょうかという感じなんですか？
I wonder who's gonna win this?
負けませんよ。
I won't lose!
私も負けないよ。
I won't lose either!
Level 1
こちらに
Over here,
動かない的があるので、こちらをみんなで1人ずつ撃っていこうかなと思います。
there are stationary targets, so we'll each shoot them one by one.
がんばる！
I'll do my best!
じゃあ、順番どうしましょう？
So, what order should we go in?
1番！
First!
やりたい！やりたい！やりたい！やりたい！やりたい！
I want to! I want to! I want to!
まつりちゃんは第1希望
Matsuri-chan gets her first choice.
じゃあ、残りの3人にはね、ここらへんで見て待ってもらいましょう。
The rest of you, watch and wait around here.
はーい。
Okay.
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
うま！うま！
Good! So good!
ごめん！
Sorry!
ごめん！え？
Sorry! Huh?
はずしなし？え？
No misses? Huh?
まつりちゃんがパーフェクトおじさんじゃん？
Is Matsuri-chan a perfect old man?
パーフェクトおじさんじゃん？
A perfect old man?
うまっ！
So good!
うまっ！え？うますぎる！
So good! Huh? Too good!
やばい。うますぎる。
So crazy. Too good.
残り15秒！えー！？
15 seconds remaining! What?!
これ、みんなにはわかんないけど、これ全部死んだかんね、これ。
You guys might not get it, but all of these are dead now.
やばい、やばい、やばい。
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
音符とかもなしに
Even notes and stuff are gone.
え、これ最後？
Huh, is this the last one?
え？え？はずした？
Huh? Huh? Did she miss?
はずしてこ？うそっ！
Should we miss? No way!
うそっ！うそっ！すごい！
No way! No way! Amazing!
まつりちゃん、すごい！無敵！
Matsuri-chan is amazing! Invincible!
まつりちゃん！
Matsuri-chan!
1発もはずさずすべて取れました！
She didn't miss a single shot and got them all!
クリア！やばすぎろ！
Clear! That's way too amazing!
うますぎるよね。
She's way too good, right?
なんかちょっと行きづらいわ。
Makes it a bit hard to go next.
私いく。
I'll go.
お待ち？
Wait?
じゃあ、トワ様が次で、次うーあ、トワ様ね。
Next is Towa-sama, then... wait, Towa-sama.
じゃあ、トワは
Then Towa,
がんばれ！
Do your best!
がんばる！
I'll do my best!
支えるよ、支える感じで。
I'll support you, supportive style.
じゃあ、カウントする？
Shall I count?
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
ここ！
Here!
はい！
Yes!
ここ！
Here!
ここ！よし、よし、よし。
Here! Good, good, good.
はやい、はやい。はい、ここ！
Fast, fast. Yes, here!
はい！ここ！
Yes! Here!
ここ！
Here!
はやい！正確と！
Fast! Accurate!
はい、ここ！
Yes, here!
ここ！
Here!
え？ちょっと待って！
Huh? Wait a second!
どういうこと？うまい、うまい、めっちゃ速い！
What do you mean? Good, good, super fast!
ここ！
Here!
うまい！
Good!
え？お前！
Huh? You!
ここ！
Here!
え？やば！はや！
Huh? No way! Fast!
クリア！おめでとう！
Clear! Congratulations!
だんだん超えてくんだ、これ。
They keep exceeding it, this.
あー、これは。
Ah, this is...
じゃあ、次どうする？
So, what should we do next?
いやー！
No way!
先にやってほしい。先にやってほしい。
I want you to go first. I want you to go first.
いや、さっきのがさ、さっきのがさ。
No, earlier, earlier...
やっぱ取り返す。
Gotta take it back.
とりあえずね、下半身作戦。下半身作戦。
Anyway, lower body strategy. Lower body strategy.
下半身を安定させ、ブレないようにする。
Stabilize the lower body so it doesn't shake.
下半身支え付けたと
When I anchored the lower body,
ポーズダッセぇ！
that pose is so lame!
ダサい。
So lame.
ダサすぎる！
Way too lame!
これで行くから。
I'm going with this.
3、2、1、どうぞ！
3, 2, 1, Go!
がんばれ！
Do your best!
よし、がんばれ！
Alright, do your best!
がんばれ！がんばれ！
Do your best! Do your best!
がんばれ！安定して。
Do your best! Stay stable.
あぶな、あぶな。
Close, close.
いってる、いってる。
It's hitting, it's hitting.
やばい、やばい。
Oh no, oh no.
いや適当に撃つ。
I'm just shooting randomly.
あ、でも惜しい！
Ah, but so close!
惜しい！惜しい！
Close! Close!
そうなに？そうなに？うつるの。
What? What? It's hitting.
上！上！
Up! Up!
がんばれ、がんばれ！
Do your best, do your best!
いや、それとらんだぞ。
No, you gotta get those.
よし！
Alright!
タイムズアップ！
Time's up!
ラプラスの成果は、まあ2ポイントとなります。
La+'s result is... about 2 points.
最後、いきますか。
Finally, shall we go?
いくで！
Let's go!
がんばれ！がんばれ！
Do your best! Do your best!
ということで、じゃあ最後、ルタ、じゃあ打ち合わせ。
So, finally Ruta, let's discuss.
あ、1秒で1秒で。
Ah, 1 second, 1 second.
1秒は嫌だ。嫌だ嫌だ嫌だ。
1 second is no good. No no no no.
準備OK？準備OK。
Ready? Ready.
行くよ。
Here we go.
じゃあ、3、2、1、ゴー！
Then, 3, 2, 1, Go!
うわあ！
Woah!
やばい！とっとととと！
Hurry, hurry!
おい、おい！
Hey, hey!
すごい！3個目？
Amazing! 3rd one?
いいよ、いいよ。思ったよりうまい！
Good, good. Better than expected!
うまいよ！
Good job!
いや、これは
No, this is...
うまい！
Good!
まだ全然余裕、余裕。
Still totally fine, fine.
まだ、まだ、まだ、まだ。
Still, still, still.
行くぞ！
Here we go!
まだ、まだ、まだ、まだ！
Still, still, still, still!
どこだ？どこだ？
Where is it? Where is it?
右、右、右！
Right, right, right!
すす、すす、すすす。スタッカ？
S-s-s-s. Staccato?
どこにある？どことんだ？
Where is it? Where did it fly?
あれ？おっちょこちょいだ！
Huh? Clumsy!
残んねえと？残んねえと！
Left over? Left over!
いやなんか、神様がこれ！
No, like, God helped with this!
神様が手伝ってくれたの？
Did God help you?
まいっか！
Oh well!
まつり先輩ナイスショット！
Matsuri-senpai, nice shot!
どことんだ？
Where did it fly?
なんかギリギリ滑り込みでハンパいと！
Barely slid in with half!
クリア！
Clear!
Level 2
こちらをご覧ください。
Please look over here.
動いてる！
They're moving!
めっちゃ動いてる！
They're moving so much!
むちゃくちゃ。
Ridiculous.
はい、がんばって行きましょう。
Alright, let's do our best.
じゃあ誰から行く？
So who's going first?
俺だ、俺だ、俺だ！
Me, me, me!
あたしも行きたい！
I want to go too!
難しそうだから。
Because it looks difficult.
もう行っちゃったから。
Since she already went.
じゃあラプラスから、もう行っちゃったからね。
Then from La+, since she already went.
いいんだ。
That's fine.
やっと満がちでやばい。
Finally full-on serious and dangerous.
では行きましょう、ラプラス！
Then let's go, La+!
行きますよ！
Here we go!
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
このゲームには必勝法がある。
There is a foolproof method for this game.
めっちゃ回っとるやん！
You're spinning like crazy!
ねえ、これずるい！
Hey, this is unfair!
後ろから撃ってんのヤバいって。
Shooting from behind is crazy.
当たってないよ！
It's not hitting!
見て、見て。
Look, look.
当たってないよ！
It's not hitting!
待って 腕 腕 腕
Wait, my arm, arm, arm!
ぐるぐるんだからカメラ
It spins around so much, the camera...
待って待って5秒しかないよ
Wait, wait, only 5 seconds left!
1個しかっ！
Only one!
頑張れ！頑張れ！
Come on! You can do it!
待って 1個しか無理だよ、1個
Wait, only one? That's impossible, just one?
1個って どういうことよ
What do you mean 'just one'?
あの、後ろ向きでな
Um, facing backwards, you see.
絶対行きたい！
I definitely want to go!
絶対行きたい？
You definitely want to?
行きたい行きたい！
Yes, I want to, I want to!
はい、じゃあ絶対行きます！
Okay, then I'll definitely go!
頑張って！いろはくん！
Do your best, Iroha-kun!
めざせ！
Aim for...
タブラスみたいに後ろ向かなくていい？
Do I not need to face backwards like Laplus?
ううん、大丈夫
No, it's fine.
遊びを… あ、やば
Playing... Ah, oh no.
裏面挑戦行きましょう！
Let's do the backside challenge!
Start!
これは
This is...
頑張れ！
Do your best!
当たんない！
It won't hit!
裏、裏、頑張れ！
Back, back, come on!
むずいから裏は！
The back is so hard!
いや終わってるんだけど私が
Wait, I'm already finished!
裏、裏、裏、裏
Back, back, back, back!
えっ、えっ、やばい、やばい
Eh, eh, no way, no way!
あっ、ったったったった
Ah, hit, hit, hit, hit!
裏だろ！
It's the back!
あっ、裏、裏、裏、
Ah, back, back, back!
早い！早い！早い！
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
あっ、裏面だったな
Ah, it was the backside, huh.
そうだね
That's right.
うわっ、やばい！裏、裏！
Whoa, no way! Back, back!
これはもう裏、裏からだ！
This is from the back, back!
うおおおおっ！
Uoooooh!
画面あるか？
Is there a screen?
あっ、あぶなっ！
Ah, close!
ということで、全達成、裏面です
So, complete success, on the backside.
めちゃくちゃ難しそう
It looks super difficult.
これ難しそう
This looks hard.
でも、惜しかったのもあったね
But there were some close ones too.
これ難しいよ
This is hard.
いやでも惜しかったのもあったね
Yeah, but there were close ones.
裏だったからさ
Because it was the back, you see.
裏面だったからすごいし
Since it was the backside, it's amazing.
最後嫌だからもう1回行かせてください
I hate ending like this, please let me go one more time!
もういいじゃん
It's fine, right?
もういいじゃん、もう行っちゃったもう行っちゃった
It's fine, she already went, she already went!
行っちゃったもう行っちゃった
She already went, she already went!
じゃ、祭りだ
Well then, it's Matsuri's turn.
祭り全力！いくぞ！
Matsuri's going all out! Here we go!
3、2、1、ゴー！
3, 2, 1, Go!
うわ！うまっ！
Whoa! So good!
待って！
Wait!
あっ、惜しい！
Ah, so close!
今のダメだったか
Was that no good?
早くない？
Isn't it fast?
あっ、おっ、おっ、おっ、おっ！
Ah, oh, oh, oh, oh!
おい！
Hey!
2個目？
Second one?
あっ、
Ah,
はい！これ何これ、これ！
Yes! What is this, this!
そうだよね
That's right.
2個の時点でね、2個の時点で
At two, at two...
難しいんだからこれ！
This is so hard!
難しい
Hard.
うーん、うーん
Hmm, hmm.
打ってるうちどんどん時間が過ぎてて
While shooting, time just flies by.
これ後ろじゃない？後ろじゃない？
Isn't this the back? Isn't it the back?
あっ、後ろ！えっ？
Ah, the back! Eh?
さっきし、後ろじゃない？
Wasn't it the back just now?
後ろはね、もうあの…
The back is, well, um...
やばい
Oh no.
やばいです
This is bad.
弱いのだとありません
With a weak one, there's nothing.
くっそー、2個か！
Damn it, only two!
いや、2個でもすごいんだよ
No, two is still amazing.
1個だよね
It's one, right?
トワ様も達成してたぞ、あっち
Towa-sama cleared it over there too!
終わんない方がいいよ、絶対そう
It's better not to end it, definitely.
トワも思ってた、たぶん
Towa thought so too, probably.
一点突破の方がいいな
It's better to focus on a single breakthrough.
あのほうがいいな
That's better.
アドバイスを生かしてやろうかな！
Maybe I'll use that advice!
かわちん挑戦！
Let's do the cute challenge!
3、2、1、わん、ごー！
3, 2, 1, Go!
がんばれ！
Come on!
おしい、おしい！
Ah, so close!
いやま、こっち向け！
Hey, face this way!
あっ、やばい！
Ah, no way!
えっ、えっ、えっ…
Eh, eh, eh...
あっ、裏だ！
Ah, it's the back!
うーん、うーん…
Back, oh...
頑張れ！頑張れ！
Come on! Come on!
えっ、どっちだっけ？両方？
Both of them? Wait, both of them?
あと10秒！がんばれ！
Only 10 seconds left! Come on!
タイミングだ、タイミングだ！
Timing is everything!
あっ、全部！裏だ！
Ah, all of them! Back!
おい、これまずい！
Wait! This is bad!
これはマジでまずい！
This is really bad!
タイムアップ！これ死んだよ！
Time's up! She died!
これ死んだよ！
She died, right?
えっ、これくっそむずいじゃん！
Eh, this is so hard!
1枚でした。
It was one, right?
いっしょだ、こそさん。
Just one? Hey, Koso-san.
いっしょす。
Together?
後ろの人と…
The person in the back...
Level 3
普通の的と動く的と来てなんと、こちら！ボーン！
From normal to moving targets, and what's this? Here!
動くマット、ゾンビだ！
Moving mat—it's a zombie!
動くマットになってます
It's a moving mat.
でも、的自体は2つしかないから、確かに
But there are only two targets, so...
あのこちらを狙ってなんか気持ち悪いポーズもしてますけど
Aiming for this, it's doing some creepy poses too.
時間差、時間差だな
Time difference, a time difference.
トワチンからじゃ行きましょう！
Towa-chin, let's go!
Start!
え、なんかおそい
Eh, it's kind of slow.
え、ごめん
Eh, sorry.
え、いける、いける、いける、いける！
Eh, we can do it, we can do it!
あっ、でもなんか… おい！おい！
Ah, but somehow... Hey! Hey!
こっち向いて！こっち向いて！
Face this way! Face this way!
やばい
Oh no.
いや、これちょっと待って！ちょっと待って！
No, wait a minute! Wait a minute!
とりあえず待って、やばい
First, wait, oh no.
あと1枚、頭の！
One more, on the head!
動くぞ！
It's moving!
おい！やばい、やばい、やばいけど
Hey! Oh no, oh no, oh no, but...
やばい、なんかキモいポーズが
Oh no, some creepy pose...
がんばれ！よっしゃ！
Do your best! All right!
やったー！クリア！
Yay! Clear!
すっごいギリギリだ
That was super close!
初、やっと割れました。ありがとうございます！
First time, finally cracked it. Thank you!
なんかゾンビがたまに自我を持ち始めて不思議な動きをするので皆さま注意を
Zombies sometimes gain self-awareness and move strangely, so everyone please be careful.
行きたい！行きたい！
I want to go! I want to go!
じゃあ、じゃあ2ちゃんね
Well then, number 2, right?
頑張るぞー！
We'll do our best!
じゃあ祭りちゃ！
Well then, Matsuri-chan!
3、2、1、どうぞ！
3, 2, 1, Go!
Start!
はやっ！はやっ！
So fast! So fast!
えっ？えっ？
Eh? Eh?
はやっ！
So fast!
3秒で終わりました！
It ended in 3 seconds!
3秒！3秒で！
3 seconds! In 3 seconds!
ああ！
Ah!
だめだ！
No good!
あれ、ちょっと、これ、これもう落ち込んでるよ。
Wait, look, it's already getting down.
これまずいよ！
This is bad!
あ、これ？
Ah, this?
え、やっちゃった、やっちゃった。まずいよこれ。
Oh, I messed up. This is bad.
今、まつりちゃんが3秒で打ち抜いちゃったということは、あの多分次ゾンビはこの動きしちゃいけないなっていうふうになって
Since Matsuri-chan wiped it out in 3 seconds, that probably means the next zombie shouldn't move like that...
ええ、やばい、学習するタイプだ。やばい、学習しちゃいます。学習ゾンビなんだ。
Eh, oh no, it's the learning type. Oh no, it's learning. It's a learning zombie!
ちょっと待って、じゃあ先にやる、先にやる。
Wait, then let me go first.
じゃあ先にやる！
I'll go first!
先にやる！先にやる！
I'll go first! I'll go first!
やった。主役が最後なんだね。
Yay. The main character goes last, huh?
主役最後なんでしょ？
The main character is last, right?
3、2、1、スタート！
3, 2, 1, start!
やばい！やばい！やばい！
No way! No way! No way!
当たるんかい！なんで当たるんだよ！
It hits?! Why does it hit?!
なんで当たるんだよ！
Why does it hit?!
やばい！
No way!
当たりそう！当たりそう！
It's gonna hit! It's gonna hit!
頭だけだよ！
Only the head!
打て打て打て！
Shoot, shoot, shoot!
当たれ！
Hit!
おお！当たるぞ！
Oh! It's gonna hit!
頑張れ、頑張れ！当たりそう！
Do your best! It's gonna hit!
あと3秒で？
With 3 seconds left?
うわあ！
Whoa!
やばい、ちょっと途中我慢できなかった。
Oh no, I couldn't hold it in midway.
ムカつきすぎて。
I got too annoyed.
最後の挑戦は、ゼータ！
The final challenge is Zeta!
3、2、1、ゴー！
3, 2, 1, go!
うわ！めっちゃ動いてる！
Whoa! It's moving so much!
当たってる！当たってる！めっちゃ動いてるよ！
It's hitting! It's moving so much!
私も撃たなきゃ！
I have to shoot too!
あと1人だ！
One more left!
いやいや、これはホルロサイズ…
No way, this is holorize...
あと1ミリ！譲らない！
Just 1 millimeter! I won't yield!
かわいい！
Cute!
いやー、やばい！すごかった！
Man, oh no! That was amazing!
よかったー！
I'm so glad!
本当に！
Really!
ちょ、めちょかるだった、ゼータ。
That was super cool, Zeta.
2ポイントでさ！やったー！すごい！
With 2 points! Yay! Amazing!
みんなー！
Everyone~!
Should we see who got the most points in this test?!
え、まつりが12点。
Eh, Matsuri got 12 points.
はい。で、トワちゃんが11点。
Yes. And Towa-chan got 11 points.
はい。で、ゼータが10点。
Yes. And Zeta got 10 points.
そしてラプラスが！14点！
And La+ got! 14 points!
14点！14点！
14 points! 14 points!
ラプラスが最下位！
La+ is in last place!
いや違う！1位はで、1位の方を選んでよ！
No wait! 1st place is—choose the 1st place!
Wooow! Congrats!
You guys did very well! And best of all, I'm glad everyone had fun. I can't wait to see how much more you can improve your aiming skills in the future, like me.
ごぼみたいにうまくなれるといいね。
Hope you can get as good as Kobo.
おい！ちょっと！
Hey! Wait a minute!
Um, I'm... I'm talking here.
おい！こぼの話を聞いてよ！
Hey! Listen to Kobo!
ま、とにかくゼータ！
Well, anyway, Zeta!
You still have a long, long way to go to become a full-fledged secret agent, okay?
まだまだ遠い道のりだよ？いい？うん、勝負しよっ！
Still a long way to go, okay? Yeah, let's have a match one day!
Bye! See ya~ バイバイ！またね～
Bye! See ya~ Bye-bye! See you later~
いや、まだまだ終わったことじゃない！
No, it's not over yet!
やばいやばいやばい！みんな気をつけて！逃げるよ！
Oh no! Everyone watch out! Run away!
おい！行くからね！逃げた、逃げた！
Hey, we're going! They ran, they ran!
That was such a crazy... I got wet! 濡れちゃったよ from the water gun. 私シューティング like crazy. I even had to change my clothes!
That was such a crazy... I got wet! I got all soaked from the water gun. I was shooting like crazy. I even had to change my clothes!
But I heard there's going to be announcements today. So, are you guys ready for the announcements? A little add break, yes?
But I heard there's going to be announcements today. So, are you guys ready for the announcements? A little ad break, yes?
では！告知です！お願いします！
Now then, it's time for announcements! Please!
Woah! So shiny! She's shining so bright, oh my god! Zeta in an angel-like outfit. Isn't that so cute? Angel costume?
You guys have always said that you're scared of me, so you can't be scared of me now, cause I'm... I'm... I mean, I'm kind of... I'm the safest... um, person there is, so...
Seiso Zeta! Seiso Zeta came! How is it? Cute? Right, it's pure white! The costume looks so cute, right?
Seiso Zeta came! How is it? Cute? Right, it's pure white! The costume looks so cute, right?
Beli bakalan guys, karena kapan lagi bisa lihat Seiso Zeta ya guys ya, berkostum, bercosplay sebagai angel-angel gitu, lucu. Iya ya Zeta lucu-lucu. Aku mau, siapa yang mau? Aku aku!
You guys should buy it, because when else can you see Seiso Zeta, guys, in costume, cosplaying as little angels, so cute. Yeah, Zeta is so cute. I want one, who wants one? Me, me!
But we don't stop here because obviously there's going to be so many more items and we're going to introduce them now. Ja! こちらをご覧ください！どうぞ！
But we don't stop here because obviously there's going to be so many more items and we're going to introduce them now. Well then, please take a look at this! Here you go!
And that amount, but that's probably six, right? Isn't that so awesome?!
Let's gooo!
So we have acrylic diorama,
So we have an acrylic diorama,
which you can put on your table later, we'll explain.
And we have a cap, uwee cap, okay?
And we have a cap, a uwee cap, okay?
We have a plushie, nouigurumi!
We have a plushie, a nouigurumi!
And not only that, there will of course be
a voice pack,
and also bonus card as well!
and also a bonus card as well!
Who wants bonus cards? Me!
So, I bet you guys are interested in this,
yeah definitely.
Kalau kalian tertarik bakal ada 6 item ya guys,
If you're interested, there'll be 6 items, guys,
acrylic diorama, haori, kucing, eh topi,
acrylic diorama, haori, cat, eh cap,
ada juga boneka, bonus card, this is also bonus card.
there's also a plushie, bonus card, this is also a bonus card.
So, yeah, definitely we're going to get into it,
but stay, stay there.
We're not, we're not done yet. We're not done yet.
Hai, segi dozo!
Alright, next, please!
Tazaong!
Ta-da!
This is my acrylic diorama stand.
So cute!
Arigato mama Sensei! Thank you so much Sensei!
Thank you so much, Mama Sensei! Thank you so much, Sensei!
Mama arigato!
Thank you, Mama!
Mama's drawing is always so cute!
Kawaii desho ne?
Isn't it cute?
Kawaii!
Cute!
Zeta tonderu yo!
Zeta is flying!
Sugoku nai?
Isn't it amazing?
It's super duper cute!
I'm having an, I was, I almost said allergic reaction.
I'm having an—I almost said allergic reaction.
I am having a, do you know that cuteness aggression? Yeah.
That's what I'm feeling.
It's so cute! Okay?
Of course, we're going to go to the next one, there's so much more.
Ja, segi dozo!
Now, next, please!
Tazaong!
Ta-da!
Nanda to? Haori!
What is this? A haori!
This, Vestia Zeta Haori!
This is the Vestia Zeta Haori!
I know that you guys would love to wear this at like events or like concerts,
I know that you guys would love to wear this at like events or concerts,
or maybe, you know, for, for future fests, uh next fest.
or maybe, you know, for future fests, uh, next fest.
You guys can wear it together.
You can like huddle up, wear the same haori.
You can huddle up and wear the same haori.
And it would be so cute, right?
I mean, I'm wearing a uniform, so you guys can be, this can be your uniform.
I mean, I'm wearing a uniform, so this can be your uniform.
Live no toki to ka.
Like during lives or anything.
So, kawaii desho?
So, isn't it cute?
Like, if everyone like use it together, it's going to be so cute.
If everyone wears it together, it's going to be so cute.
Lucu banget guys haori.
It's so cute, guys, the haori.
Aku enggak tahu mau ngomong apa, pokoknya ini keren banget karena desainnya itu pertama simpel.
I don't know what to say, it's just really cool because the design is simple first.
Terus belakangnya tuh kelihatan Zeta.
And the back shows Zeta.
Enggak norak gitu loh guys, kayak keren aja, kayak simpel, keren, cool.
And it's not tacky, guys, just cool, simple, and cool.
Jadi kalian juga pakainya bisa ke mana aja, enggak harus kayak konser-konser doang.
So you can wear it anywhere, not just for concerts.
You can like wear this like outside of concerts as well
You can wear this outside of concerts as well,
cuz like it's like a sophisticated, I would say elegant. It's like a cool looking, like tone down haori, you know.
because it's a sophisticated, I want to say elegant—a cool-looking, toned-down haori, you know.
So be fitting for me, the coolest secret agent.
So, it's fitting for me, the coolest secret agent.
Okay, and anyways, there's more! There's more!
Sugiki no, dozaong!
Next, ta-da!
Tazaong! Wow, uwee!
Ta-da! Wow, uwee!
Uwee cap! I almost choked on myself!
It's so good!
It's a baseball cap, it's so cool!
You can use this to shield yourself from the sun, like I do because I hate the sun.
There's like uwee written on top of the, kayak "uwee katteru yo", so so so so, Zeta no serifu "uwee" tte kaite iru, kawaii desho!
There's "uwee" written on top, like "uwee katteru yo", so Zeta's catchphrase "uwee" is written on it, isn't it cute?
Of course, there's like my neko, ah not neko, my hair buns, kuping, kuping Zeta, there's my hair buns there and my my, um ribbon, I would call this ribbon, ignore the whiskers, but, um, if you can ignore the whiskers,
Of course, there's my neko—ah, not neko, my hair buns, Zeta's ears, my hair buns there and my ribbon—I'd call this a ribbon, ignore the whiskers, but if you can ignore the whiskers,
those are not cat whiskers, but it's cute!
You can wear it a cap!
You can wear it as a cap!
Buy this cap, it's a good cap, no cap!
Haha, so cute!
Topi ya guys, apalagi panas-panas, harus pakai topi gaes ya guys, panas-panas.
It's a cap, guys, especially when it's hot, you gotta wear a cap, guys, when it's hot.
Apalagi silau gitu, keren kalau pakai topi loh guys.
Especially when it's glaring, it's cool to wear a cap, guys.
Terus keren lagi, hitam gitu topinya, keren-keren-keren. Masih ada kah, ya? Ada, aku tunggu.
And it's cool, the cap is black, super cool. Is there more? Yeah, I bet.
Ya, segi, dozo!
Now, next, please!
Ugh...
I, ugh, it's like, it's so cute!
It's a really cute the cat headcount. It's, it's a, it's called the Sleepy Cat Zzz Plushie!
It's a really cute cat... it's called the Sleepy Cat Zzz Plushie!
it looks like a cat I know, but I swear it's not. Okay, it's not. It's um...
If you notice, it's based on my Cat Day uh KV, so it's so cute, right?
If you notice, it's based on my Cat Day KV, so it's so cute, right?
みんな... あの、Cat Day の時を覚えてる？
Everyone... Um, do you remember Cat Day?
This is the good from uh last time.
This is the goods from last time.
It's so cute, right? Look at those eyes.
It's so cute! I want to squish it and... you know, jumble it up. It's so cute!
And she's like sleeping because um... uh I heard that cats nap for 16 hours, although that has nothing to do with me, I'm just saying.
And she's like sleeping because... um, I heard that cats nap for 16 hours, although that has nothing to do with me, I'm just saying.
It's very cute, it's like sleeping.
うん、眠そう、眠そうぜたちゃん、眠いぜたちゃん、かわいい！
Yeah, looking sleepy, sleepy Zeta-chan, sleepy Zeta-chan, so cute!
Buy it, or else... or else you you don't want to miss this because everyone like the um Cat Day KVs, you won't miss this, okay?
Buy it, or else... or else you don't want to miss this because everyone who liked the Cat Day KVs won't want to miss this, okay?
Even more, let's see,
next place, sugi!
next, please!
お願いします！
Please!
Voice... wa... voice...
voice, and it's titled A Fateful Meeting.
Last but not least, there's also a bonus for who purchases the full set.
Okay, full set...
買った人がボーナスをもらえるぞ！
Those who buy it will get a bonus!
Okay, okay. 買った人、Full Set, OK? Ja!
Okay, okay. Those who buy the full set, okay? Ja!
Last one, please. 最後、お願いします！
Last one, please. Saigo, onegaishimasu!
Tada! Here's a bonus! Wow, it's a limited edition! You'll get my signature, okay?
It's so good! It's like Yandere Signature and all that. Ugh, it's the best! It's limited, so get it now!
limited... スペシャルだよね、一番、うん、スペシャル...
Limited... It's special, right? The best, yeah, special...
Of course, um, it's a little heartbreak, but we're not going to stop there because...
Of course, um, it's a little heartbreaking, but we're not going to stop there because...
I, even though it's my birthday, I want to give to you instead. Yeah!
これでも終わりじゃないよ？
It's not over yet, you know?
It's my birthday, but I also want to give you a present as well. So...
Aren't you excited? Okay, let's go get your present!
Are you guys ready?!
goin' goin' my way もうほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone
止められない熱身任せて
Yielding to this unstoppable passion
こりごりだ rule は break it down
I'm sick of rules, so break it down
我慢できない let me free
I can't hold back, let me free
目が眩んでしまいそういてたたちのマーメイド
A mermaid of tales that seemed to dazzle my eyes
焦がれてたけど but then 今は何も響かない
I used to yearn for it, but then now nothing resonates
i know who i am ai
I know who I am
「ブランディング」にはあかかんべー
Thumb my nose at "branding"
今は完全無視よ 何でもアリのgreedy style
Now completely ignoring it, anything goes greedy style
ダサいヤッカミも興味ないのありのままでいたい
I don't care about tacky jealousy, I just want to be myself
goin' goin' my way もうほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone
止められない熱身任せて
Yielding to this unstoppable passion
こりごりだ rule は break it down
I'm sick of rules, so break it down
我慢できない let me free
I can't hold back, let me free
we are special でしょ？
We are special, right?
揺るがない pride それだけでいい の
An unshakeable pride, that's all I need
たらればだらけの low な日々 を
These low, what-if-filled days
break it down, break it
we are special でしょ？
We are special, right?
誰に言われても 私は歌うよ
No matter what anyone says, I will sing
アンフェアばかりのセカイ など
A world full of unfairness and such
break it down, break it ススメ
Break it down, break it, push forward
break it down, break it すすめ
Break it down, break it, advance
i just don't care about you !
I just don't care about you!
ハイテクなメイクや ファッション も
High-tech makeup and fashion too
self-love には敵わないよ この身と心 誰の物でもないでしょ
Can't compare to self-love, this body and soul belong to no one else, right?
いい加減に大人だよね？
We're adults already, right?
inilaha ku apa adanya, tidak sempurna, tapi sepenuhnya diriku
Here I am just as I am, imperfect, but fully myself
でも今は楽しいよ ありのままでいられるから！
But now I'm happy because I can be myself!
goin' goin' my way もうほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone
止められない熱身任せて
Yielding to this unstoppable passion
こりごりだ rule は break it down
I'm sick of rules, so break it down
我慢できない let me free
I can't hold back, let me free
we are special でしょ？
We are special, right?
揺るがない pride それだけでいい の
An unshakeable pride, that's all I need
たらればだらけの low な日々 を
These low, what-if-filled days
break it down, break it
we are special でしょ？
We are special, right?
誰に言われても 私は歌うよ
No matter what anyone says, I will sing
goin' goin' my way もうほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone
止めらんない熱身任せて
Letting my unstoppable passion take over
こりごりだ rule は break it down
I've had enough of rules, break it down
我慢できない let me free
I can't hold back anymore, let me free
can't break me down, breaking me
break it down, break it down
break it down, breaking me
goin' goin' my way もうほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone
止めらんない熱身任せて
Letting my unstoppable passion take over
こりごりだ rule は break it down
I've had enough of rules, break it down
我慢できない let me free
I can't hold back anymore, let me free
Thank you everyone!
Let's break it down!
Take it easy, if you like it, make some noise!
MISSION COMPLETE!
MY WORLD WOULD NOT BE COMPLETE WITHOUT U, SECRETARY!
My world would not be complete without you, Secretary!
YOUR SUPPORT MEANS THE WORLD TO ME! :D
LET'S KEEP DOING MISSIONS TOGETHER, FOREVER...! :3
KEEP BREAKIN' IT DOWN!